Finding Aid for the A&M Records Records PASC-M.0269
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Music, 1917-1984; Series 5.
  - O menino triste, flt1 & 2, flgl1 & 2, tbn, gtr, pno, bass, mar, dms; ozalids (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Ob-la-di, ob-la-da, manuscript, ozalid and copies (Box 164, Folder 3)
    instrumentation: herb 1 & 2, tpt 1 & 2, tbn, s.sax, bari.sax, gtr, pno, dms, rhy
  - Odd one, lead sheet; manuscript and copies (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Ode to Bobby Hackett, 1978; lead sheet; ozalid (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Oh my little ma ma ma, 1965; lead sheet; manuscript (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Ol' Kris Kringle, manuscript (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Ola, rhy; elec. gtr.; ozalid parts and copies (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Old guitaron, 1964; manuscript (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - old heartaches (is laughing at me), holograph transparency (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - On the track of love, manuscript (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Once, manuscript (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Once a day, voice; vln; gtr; bass; pno; perc; hand-written parts and holograph transparency (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Once a loser, hand-written parts and holograph transparency (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - Once these was, hand-written manuscript (Box 165, Folder 12)
    insert classic phrase
  - Once like you, 1966; manuscript (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - One more night, ozalid manuscript (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - One more night with you, hand-written manuscript with photocopies (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - Open your eyes, you can fly, tpt; hand-written manuscript with photocopies (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - Orig!, voice; hand-written manuscript (Box 165, Folder 18)
  - Our day will come, tpt; rhy; mar; hand-written manuscript with photocopies of parts (Box 165, Folder 19)
  - Outside the gates of cerdes, 1967; manuscript (Box 165, Folder 20)
  - Papa Frio (Box 165, Folder 21)
  - Para todos, tpt; tbn; ozalid parts (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Panama, tpt; tbn; rhy; manuscript and copies (Box 166, Folder 2)
    TJB35
  - Party, hand-written manuscripts (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Pata pata, tbn; rhy; hand-written parts and copies (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Peace, 1970; ozalid (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Peace of mind, 1967; manuscript copy (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - The perfect wave, 1967; copy of manuscript (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - A person is a sometime thing, 1975; copy of manuscript (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Piano bolero, ozalid (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - Picnic, hand-written manuscripts and copies (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - Piel de Serpiente (Box 166, Folder 28)
  - Playin' on my guitar, rhy; hand-written manuscript (Box 166, Folder 12)
  - Please help me forget you (love somebody new), 1964; ozalid (Box 166, Folder 13)
  - Plucky, tbn; map; rhy; hand-written manuscript and ozalid (Box 166, Folder 14)
  - poetry man, 1973; copy (Box 166, Folder 15)
  - Poor boy, 1964; holograph transparancy (Box 166, Folder 18)
  - Portraits on the moon, ozalid (Box 166, Folder 19)
  - Pretty boy, hand-written manuscript (Box 166, Folder 21)
  - The prince of peace (a child was born), 1966; ozalid (Box 166, Folder 22)
  - Promenade (Box 166, Folder 29)
  - Puerto Rico, tpt; rhy; hand-written parts (Box 166, Folder 24)
  - Pulverize the kaiser, 1967; ozalid (Box 166, Folder 25)
  - Push and Pull (Pull and Push) (Box 166, Folder 27)
  - Queen of the road, hand-written manuscript (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - A quiet sunday, 1967; ozalid (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Quinela, hand-written manuscript (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Quiro, 1961; ozalid (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Raindrops, copies of manuscript (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Red, tbn; gtr; bjo; ozalid (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Release me, vcs; strings and accordian; ozalid, handwritten scores and parts (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Remember September, ozalid (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Repent walpurgis, 1967; manuscript (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - Ring a little later, 1967; ozalid (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - Rise, rhy; ozalid (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - Robgery, ctr; hrn; tpt; sax; tbn; fdr brass; percussion; ozalid parts (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - The robin, tpt; tbn; rhy; hand-written score and copied parts (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - Rocky mountain express, 1935; manuscript (Box 178, Folder 15)
  - Rock mountain special, ozalid, holograph transparency (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - Rollin' stone, 1964; holograph transparency (Box 178, Folder 17)
  - Rosie, 1967; manuscript (Box 178, Folder 18)
  - Ruby, fr.hrn; tpt; tbn; ozalid parts and copies (Box 178, Folder 19)
  - Sa marina, ozalid parts and holograph transparencies (Box 179, Folder 1)
    vln; vla; cli; fgl; t. sax; bri. sax.; tbn; vln; gtr; tmp; dms
  - Samba de orpheu, drm; ozalid part (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - S. Antonio J. (Box 179, Folder 24)
  - El monte sal #1, hand-written manuscript and copies (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Sal #2, hand-written manuscript and copies (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Salad days (are here again), 1967; ozalid (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Salud, amor y dinero, tpt; stg; rhy; ozalid manuscript, parts, and copies (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Salvation army, tpt; cl;tba; hand-written parts and holograph transparency (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - San Diego way, ozalid (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Sand box, tpt; tbn; rhy; hand-written parts and copies (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Save the sunlight, maracas; part copy (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - Say a prayer, 1970; manuscript copy (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - Scat, 1965; ozalid (Box 179, Folder 13)
  - The sea is my soil, tpt; tbn; pno; rhy; hand-written parts and copies (Box 179, Folder 14)
  - Seonc avenue, 1972; manuscript copy (Box 179, Folder 15)
  - Senor mouse (captain mouse) duet for piano and vibes, 1972; ozalid (Box 179, Folder 16)
  - Shades of blue, tbn; tpt; hand-written parts and copies (Box 179, Folder 17)
  - She, 1971; manuscript copy (Box 179, Folder 18)
  - She touched me, tpt; tbn; rhy (Box 179, Folder 19)
  - She wandered through the garden fence, 1967 (Box 179, Folder 20)
  - Shortcut to nowhere, holograph transparency (Box 179, Folder 21)
  - Singing in the rain, reed; hrn; tbn; vln; vcl; vla; gtr; bass; perc; ozalid parts (Box 179, Folder 22)
  - Skedaddle to Seattle, 1965; ozalid (Box 179, Folder 23)
  - Sleigh ride (intro), chor; vln; vla; celli; tbn; bass; rhy; holograph transparency, ozalid parts, copies of parts (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Slick, tpt; tbn; rhy; hand-written parts and copied parts (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Snow-train, 1964; manuscript copy (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - So dusty, ozalid (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - So goes my heart, 1960; manuscript copy (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Soft is the sparrow, 1967; ozalid (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Sol #1, tij. brass; tbn; rhy; vln; hand-written parts (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sol #2, ozalid, holograph transparency (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Someday, 1968; manuscript copy (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Someone of my own, 1964; ozalid (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Something following me, 1967; manuscript copy (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Song (a 2 type feel), ozalid (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Song for Herb, rhy; mar; hand-written manuscript, parts and copies (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Song of joy, 1975; manuscript copy (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - South east girl, manuscript copy (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - South of the border, tbn; rhy; tpt; ozalid manuscript, hand-written parts and copies (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Spanish cunt charmer, hand-written manuscript and copies (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Spanish flea, tpt; tbn; rhy; hand-written parts, ozalid parts (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Spanish fly, ozalid (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Spanish gypsies, 1964; ozalid (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Take a letter Maria, 1969; ozalid (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Second Avenue (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Spanish Harlem, marimba; Ozalid print of part (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Spanish Nights (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Spanish town, lead sheet; copies (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Star sounds, 1964; lead sheet; ozalid (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Still life, lead sheet (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Strangers from heaven, gtr A & B, Tpt 1 & 2, Tbn, Cb, Batt, Dms; ozalid (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Street life, rhy; ozalid (Box 25, Folder 9)
    with pencil annotations
  - Streets of London, 1970; lead sheet (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Strike up the band, lead sheet, piano and voice; manuscript and copies (Box 25, Folder 11)
    there is also a published copy in this folder
  - The strong man, 1963; lead sheet; ozalid (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Strong strong wind, 1974; lead sheet (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Struttin' with Maria, tpt, tbn, rhy; manuscript and copies (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Summer, lead sheet; manuscript (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Summertime, lead sheet, tpt 1 & 2, tbn, pno, gtr, bass, dms; manuscript and copies (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Sundown lady, lead sheet; copy of manuscript (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Sunny, lead sheet, tpt, tbn; manuscript and copies (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Surfer queen, 1963; lead sheet; ozalid (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Surfin, perc; manuscript (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Sweet Lorraine, 1928; piano and voice (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Sweet sahara Sue, lead sheet; copy (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Sweetener (Box 75, Folder 53)
  - Symphony of love, 1968; lead sheet; ozalid (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Taco holiday, tpt; ozalid (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Take a letter Maria, 1969; ozalid (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Talk to the animals, tpt; rhy; ozalid parts and copies, hand-written lyrics and copies (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tango, tpt; hand-written part (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Taste of honey, A, ozalid parts, holograph transparency (Box 26, Folder 5)
    woodwind; tpt; hrn; tbn; vln; vla; vcl; bass; perc; rhy
  - Tear it on down, 1968; manuscript copy (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Tender care, 1975; manuscript copy (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Thanks for the memories, tbn; bass; dms; manucript copies and ozalid (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - That read head gal, 1923; manuscript (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - That's what makes the music play, 1975; manuscript copy (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Thea (look at the mess we made), 1975; manuscript copy (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - There never was a time, 1968; manuscript (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - There're many stops along the way, 1977; manuscript copy (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - There's a love, 1980; manuscript copy (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - These are the ways of love, 1965; ozalid (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - This love, your love, my love, ozalid manuscript, parts and copies (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - This time last summer, 1965; ozalid (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Thoroughly modern millie, 1966; ozalid manuscript, parts, and copies (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Three empty glasses, manuscript copies (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Tico taco, hand-written manuscript and ozalid (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Tijuansa brass tango, 1967; ozalid (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Tijuana frug, 1965; ozalid (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - The time has come for summer, hand-written manuscript (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Time it was, tbn; gtr; pno; bass; dms; ozalid parts and copies (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Time will tell, 1972; Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - TJ taxi, tpt., tbn., rhy.; manuscript parts (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - To be loved by me, Ozalid prints of lead sheet (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - To her face, tbn; manuscript part (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - To wait for love (is to waste your life away), 1963; manuscript, holograph transparencies, and Ozalid prints of parts and lead sheet (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Instrumentation: voices (girls & boys), vln., vla., Herb, tpt., tbn., gtr., bass, pno., perc., dms.
  - Tomatoes (the odd couple), organ, strings, bass, perc.; Ozalid print of score (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Tomorrow, manuscript and photocopy of lead sheet (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Tomorrow will be better, tbn., bass, rhy.; manuscript and photocopied parts (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Tonight we love, vln., vcl.; Ozalid prints of score (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Too young to go surfing, Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Town without pity, lead sheet, tpt, tbn, rhy; holograph transparancies, manuscripts, and ozalid copies of parts (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Train, lead sheet, tpt, tbn; manuscript and copies (Box 27, Folder 15)
    also says "brass are coming" on first page
  - This that 'n the other, lead sheet (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Trains, boats and planes, ozalid (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Travel bureau, ozalids (Box 27, Folder 18)
    instrumentation: conductor, vln, vla, vcl, sax 1,2,3,4 & 5, harp, bass, perc
  - Treasure of san miguel, tpt, tbn, rhy; manuscript and copies (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Trigal, 1969; lead sheet; ozalid and copy (Box 27, Folder 21)
    copy is published
  - Trolley song, manuscript and copies (Box 27, Folder 22)
    instrumentation: lead sheet, tpt, tbn, vln, vla, gtr, bass, dms, rhy
  - The trouble with hello is goodbye, lead sheet; copy (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Tryin' to get the feeling again, 1974; lead sheet; copies (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Tup a tup, tpt, tbn, rhy; manuscript and copies (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Turn around, lead sheet; manuscript (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Twenty below, 1970; lead sheet; ozalid (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Under the blanket, original manuscipts and photocopies (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Under the sun, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 28, Folder 2)
    From Oscar Brown, Jr.'s "JOY" - A musical come-together
  - Alpert & turner's unfinished symphony, holograph transparencies and original manuscript (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Until its time for you to go, 1965; Ozalid prints of parts (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Un-wanted, the, original manuscript (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Up cherry street, Tpt; rhy; clar.; original manuscripts and photocopies (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Up on the roof, Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Up, up and away, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Upstairs downstairs (theme from), 1973 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Vamos, Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Vento bravo, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Victor herbert, theme for, original manuscript (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Wade in the water, tpt; tbn; rhy; original manuscripts and photocopies (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Wailing of the willow, the, original manuscript and photcopies (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Wait for me mary, 1942; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Waiting to be, original manuscript (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Waking-up sun, 1967; ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Walk don't run, tpt; tbn; rhy; original manuscipts and photocopies (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Walk thru the world, cond;hn;sax;vln;vla;vcl;cb;gtr;hp;dms;perc; Ozalid prints of parts (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Walkin' slow, original manuscript and holograph transparencies (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Wall street rag, the, 1966; tpt; tbn; rhy; ozalid print of lead sheet and photocopies of parts (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Warm, holograph transparencies, ozalid and manuscripts prints of parts (Box 29, Folder 1)
    bass fl; flugel; pno; gtr; dms; herb; tpt; tbn; bass
  - Washrag, photocopy score (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - We belong together, 1980; photocopy sheet music (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - We love you Bud, bone; rhy; manuscript parts and photocopies of parts (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - We're a home, 1967; Ozalid prints (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Wer'e just a couple of kids, holograph transparencies (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - What I'm gonna do, Ozalid lead sheets (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - What I've got to say, photocopy sheet music (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - What now my love, tpt; rhy; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Whatsinya, ozalid prints of lead sheet (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - When did I just become a friend, 1965; ozalid prints of lead sheet (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - When my sugar walks down the street, 1924; original lead sheet (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - When the circus comes to town, 1935; original lead sheet (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - When you fall for a guy, Ozalid prints (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Where are the angels, choir; Ozalid lead sheet (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Where do I belong, photocopy score (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Where the beat meets the street, 1983; photocopy score (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Whistle while you work, tpt; bone; rhy; holograph transparencies, ozalid and manuscripts prints of parts (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - A whiter shade of pale, 1967; photocopy score (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Who knows where the time goes?, 1969; photocopy score (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Wind song, photocopy score (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Winds of Barcelona, voice; tpt; tbn; rhy; dmn; bongos; perc; manuscript parts, photocopy of parts and ozalid copies of parts (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Windy, tpt; rhy; manuscript parts and photocopies of parts (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Winter wonderland, 1934; Chor; vcl; tbn; rhy; perc; published original, photocopies, ozalid prints of parts (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - With a little help, tpt; vcl; rhy; original manuscripts, ozalid prints of parts (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - With a prayer in you heart (and a bible in your hand), 1956; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - With love (sambalero), original lead sheet (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Without her, chor;vln;vla;vcl;gtr;pno;tpt;dms;perc; holograph transparancies and ozalid copies of parts (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Without you, tpt;bari sax; bass tbn; gtr; pno; bass; dms; original manuscript, holograph transparencies, and ozalid copies of parts (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Wolverton mt., ozalid prints of lead sheet (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Won't someone please belong to me, 1964; original manuscript and photocopies (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Wooden heart, tba; clar; perc; original manuscript and ozalid prints of parts (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Wooden shoes, bass; cb; dms; gtr; perc; original manuscript (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Work song, tpt; tbn; rhy; original manuscript (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Woyaya, 1972; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - X-1, Ozalid lead sheet (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Ye-go, Ozalid lead sheet (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Yellow daffodils, 1964; Ozalid lead sheet (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Yesterday, original manuscript of trombone part (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - You, 1964; holograph transparency of lead sheet (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - You only live twice, 1967; Ozalid lead sheet (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - You smile, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Your doin' what ya did with me with him, original manuscript of full score (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Za zoo, original manuscript (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Zazueira, tpt; tbn; rhy; gtr; pno; original manuscripts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Zei gezunt, 1956; 1961; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Zorba the greek, tpt; rhy; original manuscript, photocopies of parts, and ozalid prints of parts (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Atlantic Rhythm and Blues 1947-1974, 1985; Boxed Set (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Vol. 1 (1947-1952), Vol. 2 (1952-1955), Vol. 3 (1955-1958), Vol. 4 (1958-1962), Vol. 5 (1962-1966), Vol. 6 (1966-1696), Vol. 7 (1969-1974)
  - Unidentified (Box 72)
    39 boxes of unidentified manuscript music
  - Unidentified (Box 73)
    46 folders of unidentified music manuscripts
  - Sheet music (Box 74)
    7 folders of unidentified music manuscripts
    Scope and Contents
    This box contains the following titles: Somewhere, I'll Be Back, Last Tango (Version 2), Walk Don't Run, The Nicest Things Happen, Montezuma's Revenge, The Lonely Bull, Don't Take It Away, Keepin The Heat Down, Rute 101,Just You and Me, I Will Wait for you, and unnamed music sheets.
  - Sweetning-apple jade, apple jade and silver beads (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Bajanova (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - The bell that couldn't jingle (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - The child (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Arranged by Shorty Rogers
  - Christmas song (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Continental (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Country boy (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Crazy arms (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Drivin' Fuji tecque (Box 75, Folder 9)
    ozalid manuscript
  - Favorite things (Box 75, Folder 10)
    Introduction included
  - Ferry Cross the Mersey (Box 75, Folder 11)
    Produced by Herb Alpert.
  - Georgia town (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Girl talk (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Gone (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Arranged by P. Borkin Jr. Produced by A&M Records
  - Good morning sunshine (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Greenleaves of summer (Box 75, Folder 16)
    Arranged by Herb Alpert Produced by T. J. Brass
  - Guacamole, 1965 November 15 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    Baja Marimba Band
  - Guess who (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - The heart of the stone (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Herbie's theme (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - He'll have to go (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Here come more roses (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - How's the world treating you (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - A Hundred Pounds of Clay, 1963 March 27 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Hurt so bad, 1971 February 20 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - I miss my surfer boy (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - If you could read my mind, 1971 February 20 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - I'll be back (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Its tough to... (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - I'd do it all again (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Jingle bell rock (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Jingle bells (Box 75, Folder 32)
    Includes introduction
  - John's tune (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Joli Jacquelina (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Lu virgen de la macarena (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Loes choses (Box 75, Folder 36)
    Herb Alpert
  - Let it snow/mountain (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - Los mananitas (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - Love denied (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - Love potion #9 (Box 75, Folder 40)
  - Lubat (Box 75, Folder 41)
    Percussion 3
  - Martha my dear (Box 75, Folder 42)
    mimeograph
  - Milord, 1963 March 9 (Box 75, Folder 43)
  - Most wonderful time (Box 75, Folder 44)
  - Moon tiver orchestra version (Box 75, Folder 45)
    manuscript and copies
  - No title (Box 75, Folder 46)
  - Night gown (Box 75, Folder 47)
  - The nicest things happen, 1971 February 21 (Box 75, Folder 48)
  - O mar e meu chao (Box 75, Folder 49)
  - O menino triste (Box 75, Folder 50)
  - Ob-la-di, ob-la-da (Box 75, Folder 51)
  - Once a day (Box 75, Folder 52)
  - Manuscripts, Subseries 1.
    This subseries predominantly consists of instrumental parts for songs performed by the Tijuana Brass and other ensembles led by Herb Alpert.
    - 3erd, Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - 1922, Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - 1927, bass, vibraphone; lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - A Banda, trumpet, trombone, rhythm; manuscript parts, published piano part (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Abraham, photocopied lead sheets (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Acapulco, trumpet, trombone, rhythm, piano; manuscript parts (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Adios mi corazon, trumpet, trombone, rhythm; manuscript parts and ozalid prints (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - All My Loving, trumpet, trombone, rhythm; manuscript parts and copies (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - All over again (I'm falling in love), onion skin and manuscript lead sheets (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - The Alley Cat Song, Ozalid lead sheets (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Alone again naturally, Trumpet, rhythm; manuscript parts and photocopies of parts (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Alone with you, onion skin lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Along comes Mary, Ozalid lead sheets (Box 180, Folder 15)
  - Published, Subseries 2.; 117 items
    Arrangement note
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Thirty-two feet and eight little tails, 1951; manuscript (Box 26, Folder 19)
      Plate no.: 911-3
    - This guy's in love with you, 1968; manuscript, ozalid manuscript and parts, copies of parts (Box 26, Folder 20)
      tbn; vln; vla; celli; hamonica; gtr; perc; dms; tpt; rhy
    - The tin pan alley rag, 1951; voice, piano, and chords; Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Today's disappointments, Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Traces, 1969; piano and voice (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Treasure of your love, 1958; piano and voice (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Try a little tenderness, 1932; piano and voice (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - United we stand, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Untie me, 1962 & 1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)